STAN CHAO

(604) 700-5765 | Vancouver, BC cardioforcake.dev@gmail.com https://stanchao.netlify.app/

Summary

Nine years of successful sales and customer service experience in the financial services industry. In addition to my customer facing experience, I have a strong background in mathematics and finance through post-secondary and self-directed studies.

Skills

Critical Thinking

Communication

❖ Research

- Team leadership
- Client relations
- Creativity

Work Experience

Personal Banker | Bank of Montreal

12/2015-present

- Consistently ranked among the top 15% of investment advisors in my market
- Q3 2020, Q3 2019 and Q1 2017 internal Spotlight Award winner
- Experience with every area of retail banking, including lending and financial planning
- Excelled in cultivating relationships with clients to drive business growth
- Helped to train new personal bankers

Customer Service Representative | Bank of Montreal

04/2012-12/2015

- Consistently exceeded sales and customer service targets
- Excelled in resolving customer issues and complaints

Energy Consultant | Superior Energy

05/2009-09/2011

- Experience with cold calling and door-to-door sales
- Full commission-based compensation
- Trained new sales representatives

Education and Training

ombined Major in Economics and Statistics University of British Columbia	2013
Complete Python Bootcamp Certificate Udemy.com	2021
Chartered Financial Analyst Level 1 CFA Institute	2018
Canadian Securities Course Canadian Securities Institute	2016